Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/phuc-nguyenhang-diem (LinkedIn) www.figma.com/proto/ cdWr0sjSU72byGehaPqZ95/ Portfolio---Phuc-Nguyen-Hang-Diem (Portfolio)

Top Skills

UX Research
Interaction Design
Responsive

Certifications

Graphic Design Foundations: Layout and Composition

Graphic Design Foundations: Typography

Graphic Design Masterclass - Learn GREAT Design

Google UX Design Specialization

Phuc Nguyen Hang Diem

UX/UI Designer

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Summary

I've always been passionate about design. My passion for design is what landed me a job as a UI/UX Designer. I enjoy finding new ways to improve the experience of the products I design. I'm constantly thinking about how I can improve the way my clients perceive their products.

Experience

NA.AI Studio UI/UX Designer December 2021 - Present (3 years 4 months) Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

namperfume
UI/UX Designer
December 2021 - November 2022 (1 year)
Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Kholab

1 year 1 month

UI/UX Designer

January 2021 - October 2021 (10 months)

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Assisted the design team in creating wireframes, prototypes, and mockups.

Assisted in layout adjustments based on client feedback.

Developing overall UI look and feel for web applications and mobile apps.

UI/UX

October 2020 - December 2020 (3 months)

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Following creative direction and implementation.

Follow style guidelines for fonts, colors, and images.

Communicated with others sharing all ideas and thoughts during the design process.

Education

University of Gloucestershire

Bachelor's degree, English Language and Linguistics · (2017 - 2021)